revoseek.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy | RevoSeek.com

We appreciate you for visiting **Your Revoseek.com**. Your privacy is significant to us. To better guard your privacy, we would like to share our privacy policy with you and give details how it may affect your privacy.

**What information do we collect?**

At Revoseek.com, you can view articles on various topics such as Education, Lifestyle, IT, Entertainment, Technology, Gadgets, Internet, etc. These posts offer you with a way to express your judgment by the means of a comment form at the finish of every post. These forms require your name, email address, website address (optionally) and your remarks or judgment. This set of personally identifiable information is collected by the server and processed before it’s displayed back on the article’s page.

similar to many other websites, we also use visitor tracking software (e.g [ Google](http://revoseek.com/technology/google-maps-launches-route-planning-3d/) Analytics, Alexa) that collects general non-personal information such as type of browser operating system (e.g., [ Linux](http://revoseek.com/information-technology/innovative-mouse-for-business-minded-guys/), Windows XP), type of browser (e.g., Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Internet explorer), name of your ISP (e.g., AOL, Verizon, ATT). We Also use Cookies and weblogs to maintain visitors`s non-personal information.

**What we do with the collected information at Revoseek.com?**

We do NOT put up for sale your personally restricted information such as your name, email address to any person or organization. The collected information from the comment forms are stored on our servers and are used only to display your previously submitted opinions/comments and identify your subsequent visits so that your comments are not blocked by our anti-spam plugins (e.g., Akismet).

The general non-personal information such as type of your browser, screen resolution, your country of origin etc., are used only to enhance the content of this website and customize the ads that are displayed on its pages

We may, if compulsory by law and in response to legal procedure, release your personally identifiable information. This type of information may also be disclosed to law enforcement agencies and other related government bodies.

We have taken various safeguards to guard the privacy data against any unauthorized disclosure, however we can not assure you that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner that is not consistent with this privacy statement.

**Information collected by third-parties, advertisement programs and sponsors**

We utilize third party ad-programs (e.g, Google AdSense) to serve ads on our website and all of its pages for monetization purpose. These ads contain links to other websites that may NOT follow privacy protection policies that we follow OR their privacy protection policies might vary from ours. Therefore, we recommend that you read the privacy policies of those website before you submit your information to them since we do not have any control over how they collect your information and how they process it.

**Updates to privacy policy**

The privacy statement is reviewed and updated (Without any prior notice) from time to time. We request you to periodically check and review the policy and keep yourself updated about how we collect and use your information.

**Revoseek.com**  is not accountable for any sort of harm (caused by reading posts published by **Revoseek.com** ) to hardware, software, property or Human Life.

The privacy statement posted on this website has been updated on July 19th, 2011.

We Welcome your queries and suggestions at **[info@Revoseek.com](http://revoseek.com/contact/)**.
